<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>

<questions>
  <question>I know what my purpose in life is.</question>
  <question>I am excited about learning new things and developing my skills and talents.</question>
  <question>My life is in balance physically.</question>
  <question>My life is in balance emotionally.</question>
  <question>My life is in balance spiritually.</question>
  <question>When life feels "out of control," I choose healthy behaviors to help me re-center and renew. (i.e. I do not use shopping, eating, sleeping, television / internet, or other substances to escape and cope).</question>
  <question>I am aware and enjoy living in the moment (I don't dwell on future or past events).</question>
  <question>I have fulfilling relationships with family and friends.</question>
  <question>I have fulfilling intimate relationships in my life.</question>
  <question>Humor, laughter, and playfulness are a big part of my daily life.</question>
  <question>My partnerships are fairly and equally balanced (work and personal).</question>
  <question>I find positive ways to deal with stress. (i.e. exercise, talking, meditating, etc).</question>
  <question>I exercise appropriate control over the things that I can in my life.</question>
  <question>I live life with an attitude of gratitude.</question>
  <question>I live my life with passion and joy.</question>
  <question>I have exciting dreams and aspirations to look forward to.</question>
  <question>I am an optimistic person.</question>
  <question>I enjoy hearing other people's insights and points of view, even when they are different from my own.</question>
  <question>I find it easy to forgive others when I have been hurt.</question>
  <question>I apologize and make amends quickly when I have hurt someone else.</question>
  <question>I am good at keeping events in my life in perspective.</question>
  <question>I live my life with integrity and honesty in all of my dealings.</question>
  <question>Kindness and compassion are virtues that I practice daily.</question>
  <question>I perform acts of service daily.</question>
  <question>I have a strong faith which sustains me throughout my life.</question>
</questions>
